A Guide to Records of the Office of the Attorney General of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1974-1994 (bulk 1990-1993)
Library of Virginia
- Series IV: Settlements, 19xx., Extent: 1.4 cu. ft. (4 boxes). (Box 22-25)
  - Settlements, 1992 Apr.-May (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Settlements, 1992 June (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Settlements, 1992 July-Aug. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Settlements, 1992 Sep.-Oct. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Settlements, 1992 Nov.-Dec. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Settlements, 1993 Jan.-Feb. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Settlements, 1993 Mar.-Apr. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Settlements, 1993 May-June (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Settlements, 1993 July-Aug. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Settlements, 1993 Sep.-Nov. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Settlements, 1993 Dec. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Settlements, 1994 Jan. (Box 25, Folder 5)